MD RIAJ HOSSAIN

WEB DEVELOPER



+880 1305406426

riyajhossen73@gmail.com

- Dhaka, Bangladesh
- github.com/RiyajHossen

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, BootStrap
- JavaScript, jQuery
- PHP & Laravel
- MYSQL
- WordPress
- On page SEO

EDUCATION

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

Really Great High School

August, 2020 -

December, 2022

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Really Great University

2014 - 2016

PROFILE

Hello, My name is Riaj Hossain and I'm a full-stack PHP/Laravel developer. I am 22 years old. I have just completed my Higher Secondary School Degree. In 2020 I was worried about my future then I decided to do freelance and start learning Web development from youtube. Since 2021 I have worked with 5-6 local clients on 30+ projects. My recent and active projects are RetouchPilot.com, AlbumCover.art, and BekarsWorld.com I have created everything myself on those websites. I'm honest and introvert. Now, I wish to work with you and support my family. I know I don't have the expertise you want. So give me less salary. I'm excited to learn new things as well. I am ready to work hard as per your instruction.

EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Deft Digital

2021-2022

- · Retouchpilot.com website design and development
- AlbumCover.art website design and development
- Admin, Manager, and User management

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Pkazu LTD

2020-2021

- Planning and Idea of user experience
- Website Designing
- Admin Panel Desing
- Backent Development

LANGUAGES

- English ● ● ●
- Bangla ● ● ●